(Leonard:)-You ready to go?
-Yep. Hey, and maybe this time,
(Penny:)you don't try and talk sports
with the guys.
(Leonard:)Some sports bar.
(Leonard:)It's like they never
even heard of Quidditch.
(Leonard:)Do we really have to go?
(Penny:)Oh, come on. Every time we're
about to hang out with my friends,
(Penny:)you don't want to.
It's like, "It's too loud,"
or "The bathroom's too dirty,"
or "They put a chicken wing
in my ear." I mean...
Well, you're right.
Let's just go.
(Penny:)-Hey, what's going on with you?
-Nothing, I'm fine.
(Penny:)All right, hang on.
Is this still about your mom's book?
(Leonard:)No. Not everything is about my mom.
'Cause if you're still upset
about that, we don't have to go.
(Leonard:)Except this is totally about my mom.
(Penny:)I'm so sorry.
I never should have read that book.
(Penny:)You know what? You want to just get
dinner and watch the game here?
(Leonard:)-That sounds nice.
-Okay.
(Leonard:)Or, you know, we could get take-out
(Leonard:)and watch the Blu-ray
extended version
(Leonard:)of The Hobbit movie
with commentary track.